I'll be back.
I'll be back. I'll be back.
I will be back. I'LL BE BACK.
I'LL BE BACK.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
Dinner was good.
Dinner was good. Dinner was good.
What is that monstrosity? What is that
monstrosity?
monstrosity? What is that monstrosity?
What is that monstrosity?
SHUT THE [ __ ] UP. SHUT UP.
Shut the [ __ ] up. SHUT UP. SHUT THE [ __ ]
UP. SHUT THE [ __ ] UP.
SHUT THE [ __ ] UP.
Shut the [ __ ] up. SHUT THE [ __ ] UP. SHUT
THE [ __ ] UP.
I'M IN THE HOSPITAL. I'M IN THE
HOSPITAL. I'm in the hospital. I'm in
the hospital. Yeah. But I'm in the
hospital. But I'm in the hospital.
I'm in the hospital. I'm in the
hospital. I'm in the hospital.
I'm in the hospital.
Let's try this.
>> Medical attention needed. Medical
attention needed. Medical attention
needed.
Medical attention needed.
Would you like to speak with him?
Would you like to speak with him? Would
you like to speak with him? Would you
like to speak with him?
Look,
up in the sky.
Up in the sky.
LOOK UP IN THE SKY. And look up in the
sky.
Look up in the sky. Look up in the sky.
Up in the sky.
LOOK UP IN THE SKY. LOOK UP IN THE SKY.
Are you mad?
Are you mad? Are you mad? Are you mad?